<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Vision</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">Vision</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="step0">Take a Fundus Image</string>
    <string name="step1">Explain the procedure to the patient and obtain permission. Explain that the process may take 1 - 2 min and involves shining a bright light into the eye.</string>
    <string name="step2" formatted = "false">Dilate the patient\'s pupil using a combination of mydriatic drops such as 2.5% Phenylephrine and 1% Tropicamide ophthalmic drops (one drop from each, 2 - 3 min apart, in the eye to be examined). Wait 15 - 20 min for pupils to dilate.</string>
    <string name="step3">Sit in front of the patient on a comfortable chair and be positioned 30 - 60 cm from the patient and at about the same level.</string>
    <string name="step4">Ask the patient to look at a far target with the other eye.</string>
    <string name="step5">Set the smartphone camera on video mode.</string>
    <string name="step6">Turn on the camera\'s flashlight.</string>
    <string name="step7">After darkening the room, press the camera record button on the smartphone to record a continuous video.</string>
    <string name="step8">Hold the +20 diopter (D) or any other indirect ophthalmoscopy lens in front of the patient\’s eye with your thumb and index finger. Use the middle and ring fingers to stabilize the hand and lens and to help keep eyelids open.</string>
    <string name="step9">Hold the camera 10 - 35 cm from the lens. Direct the camera along the patient\'s pupillary axis. Aim the light to the pupil and find the retina glow. Direct the light through the lens onto the retina and continue video recording.</string>
    <string name="step10">While recording, move the camera and the lens to find a good focus and an image free of light reflections. Adjust the handheld lens to and from the patient’s eye to see a clear retina image filling the entire lens area. NOTE: In our experience, the lens should be held 3 - 5 cm from the eye (this is slightly further away from the cornea surface compared to what is appropriate for an indirect ophthalmoscopy exam).</string>
    <string name="step11">Try to eliminate unnecessary light reflections by adjusting the camera and lens positions. Losing the image while searching the retina means that the camera and its flash light are not aligned with the handheld lens and pupil. It takes practice to keep the camera, handheld lens, and patient pupil aligned.</string>
    <string name="step12">Continue to record video until a good view of the area of interest without significant light reflections and aberrations is captured.</string>
    <string name="step13">Stop the recording and ask the patient to sit back and be comfortable.</string>
    <string name="step14">Re-play the recorded movie until there is a good retina view within the handheld lens area. Stop the movie and take a screen shot of the view.</string>
    <string name="step15">Magnify the screen shot and take another screen shot for a larger retina image. Like an indirect ophthalmoscope view, this image is inverted.</string>
</resources>
